<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Literature on Misaka's Secrect Garden</title><link>https://blog.moeomu.com/categories/literature/</link><description>Recent content in Literature on Misaka's Secrect Garden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:00:20 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.moeomu.com/categories/literature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dream Recollection - Dream as Life, I Desire You</title><link>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/dream-recollection-dream-as-life-i-desire-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:00:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/dream-recollection-dream-as-life-i-desire-you/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.statically.io/gh/Misakaou/imagestorage@master/20230929/webpageheadimageLiterature_84636833.3nwqlcfdnx4w.5zkk04m0znnk.webp" alt="Featured image of post Dream Recollection - Dream as Life, I Desire You" />&lt;p>Source of this article: &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/dream-recollection-dream-as-life-i-desire-you/" >MoeomuBlog&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="background">Background&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>This is a slightly darker plot, a revenge story and a tragedy at the same time, so let me know if you don&amp;rsquo;t like it, please!&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>In the past ten years, a foreign general and I were entangled in a tumultuous love-hate relationship. Ten years ago, he killed all my loved ones, leaving me devastated. And now, after a decade of planning, I have brought destruction upon his kingdom. With the cloud-shaped dagger he had once given me, I plunged it into his heart.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="ten-years-ago">Ten years ago&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The general stood tall, accompanied by his colossal giant guardians, resembling mountains of steel. They wielded their dual hammers, mercilessly destroying my homeland. I will forever remember the image of my grandfather, torn apart and lifeless, his body mangled, and his eyes filled with despair. Trembling with fear, I hid behind a massive rock, praying not to be discovered. Unfortunately, I, along with a few survivors, were captured and taken to prison. On our way, a tightly wrapped officer thoroughly searched every pocket. The general had triumphed in this battle. The seed of hatred sprouted within me as I stared fiercely at him, inspecting the spoils of war in the prison. His eyes were as cold and merciless as a sharpened blade, his demeanor as frigid as an ancient iceberg. He did not see me; his gaze was consumed by thoughts of war and glory.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I began plotting my escape. While discussing with my fellow inmates how to break free, one of them mentioned having a small knife that could cut through the somewhat unreliable locks. However, she underestimated the resilience of these seemingly simple locks. After several attempts, we gave up. Feeling lost, I absentmindedly reached into my pocket and discovered an Ender Pearl. Though unsure of its purpose, I knew it had the power of teleportation. Without hesitation, I flung it towards the iron bars, and as expected, after a moment of dizziness, I found myself outside the prison walls.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="spanning-the-decade">Spanning the decade&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Covered in dirt and grime, I was taken in by a kind-hearted family, finally finding a home once again. Unfortunately, the fleeting moments of happiness were cut short as we were separated during the chaotic times of war and displacement. To survive, I resorted to singing in small taverns, scraping by on meager earnings. Luckily, I caught the attention of the royal court&amp;rsquo;s musical ensemble, who were conducting a civilian talent show on the streets in order to unite the people. And so, I became a member of the royal song and dance troupe.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Over the years, I gradually learned the art of singing and dancing. The sudden leap in social status was difficult to adjust to, but it also provided me with the opportunity to engage in other activities. I learned how to charm the nobles, using my eyes to captivate them, every smile and gesture stirring their hearts and desires. In addition, I spent my remaining time assisting at the monastery, forming a close bond with the nuns and gaining the chance to study medicine. The nuns warned me to be cautious in my actions, to let kindness guide me, as any misstep could invite plague, a divine punishment, a devastating calamity.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As fate would have it, the general, at the request of the royal family, arrived at the palace to witness the court&amp;rsquo;s performances. His countenance remained stern, his deep blue eyes as captivating as the boundless sky. On that night, as I danced with grace and sang with beauty, his gaze seemed to soften, filled with tenderness. From that day forward, he sought me out in private, but I refused his advances for various reasons, resorting to exchanging letters instead.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>His desire to see me grew stronger, leading him to invite the royal court to his ducal estate. Naturally, the royal orchestra accompanied them to liven up the occasion. As the night drew to a close, I found myself intercepted by guards on the way, escorted to the general&amp;rsquo;s private reception room. When he saw me enter, his sharp eyebrows softened, his deep indigo eyes brimming with affection. He looked at me and said, &amp;ldquo;Why have you been avoiding me? What worries you?&amp;rdquo; I immediately feigned a distressed expression and replied, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m truly afraid.&amp;rdquo; Gently, he pulled me into his arms, and I offered no resistance. &amp;ldquo;Afraid of me?&amp;rdquo; he asked. &amp;ldquo;Yes,&amp;rdquo; I replied. &amp;ldquo;And now?&amp;rdquo; he inquired. &amp;ldquo;Not as much anymore.&amp;rdquo; I gazed into his captivating eyes, and he tenderly kissed my forehead.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our clandestine relationship grew stronger, our meetings more frequent. I could see the fiery desire in his eyes, burning brighter with each encounter. Soon, I would have my revenge. In my mind, I silently compared various methods of murder I had accumulated over the years, ultimately deciding on poisoning him. Referring to the records in the monastery&amp;rsquo;s library, I chose to extract KCN, a highly toxic substance, from a pigment known as Prussian Blue. I learned some basic chemistry from the nuns and, under the pretense of wanting to paint, playfully requested a large quantity of paint from the general. Back at home, following the instructions from the books, I carefully extracted a small amount of KCN, sealed it securely, and pondered its potential use in the future.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As time went by, our repeated dates made us the most familiar people to each other, apart from my childhood memories. He held me close as we admired the flowers under the night sky, seeming slightly intoxicated. &amp;ldquo;Am I more beautiful, or are the flowers?&amp;rdquo; I asked playfully. &amp;ldquo;Your smile is more beautiful than roses, and your eyes are like a deep blue ocean. Every time our gazes meet, I can&amp;rsquo;t look away. You are my most beautiful garden,&amp;rdquo; he tenderly expressed, captivating me with his words. In that moment, I fantasized about how happy we could have been if I didn&amp;rsquo;t carry the burden of hatred. Although this man&amp;rsquo;s heart was hard to fathom, sometimes appearing slightly indifferent, while other times being passionately fiery.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He invited me on another outing, presenting a rectangular mahogany box. The delicate carvings and golden exterior made it look like an unparalleled work of art. I opened the box with surprise, revealing an exquisite dagger. The ivory handle gleamed, adorned with silver threads and gemstones, resembling elegant wisps of clouds, exuding an extraordinary elegance. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t need this, take it back,&amp;rdquo; I said, feeling a surge of anger upon seeing the gift. How typical of a straight-laced man, truly befitting a duke general. &amp;ldquo;This is a token of our love, I love you, and I really want to marry you,&amp;rdquo; he spoke with a hint of urgency in his tone. &amp;ldquo;My position can only allow me to be your mistress. That&amp;rsquo;s the only way I can agree.” I replied with a smile. He seemed slightly embarrassed, a expression I had never seen on his face before. He continued, &amp;ldquo;I discussed it with my family, they won&amp;rsquo;t support it, but I can disregard my reputation and interests.&amp;rdquo; I caressed his face and asked, &amp;ldquo;Is it worth it for me?&amp;rdquo; Then, I immediately kissed him, not allowing him to say anything further.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As I looked at the token of love he had given me, I also saw the sincerity and tenderness in his eyes. In that moment, I had to admit to myself that my feelings for him had become twisted over the years. In his room, he showed me many of his diaries. He was someone who enjoyed drinking tea, and in the days that followed, I searched far and wide for authentic Eastern teas, carefully packaging them as exquisite gifts for him. He seemed to always complain that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t let him into my heart.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="now">Now&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I had someone purchase a batch of rats locally and injected them with rat blood infected with a distant plague. I knew they would suffer, just like me. I murmured to one of the little cuties, &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re really the same, aren&amp;rsquo;t we? We&amp;rsquo;re all the same. Just endure a little longer, it will all be over soon.&amp;rdquo; Standing at the entrance of my secret underground laboratory, I looked at the footprints on the lab floor and realized that someone had seemingly entered. But it didn&amp;rsquo;t matter anymore. Whoever it was, it was irrelevant. The rats had all been released, and the outcome was already predetermined.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On our final date, while he was away greeting important guests, I took out the white solid substance I had prepared. As I was about to pour it in, I hesitated. Complex emotions flooded my mind. Him and my happiness, our relationship, and the world, none of it mattered anymore. I made up my mind for revenge. I placed the white substance into the cup he often used for tea, and it dissolved instantly, leaving a hint of bitter almond taste mixed with the aroma of the tea, hoping he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t notice. After doing everything, I fell to the ground, overcome by tears streaming down my face.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When he returned, I had already composed myself. He gently held me in his arms as he sat down, then picked up the cup of tea and savored the aroma as usual before drinking it all in one gulp. Suddenly, he was wracked with unbearable stomach pain and released me, urging me to call a doctor. In one swift motion, I reached behind me and plunged the dagger of love, which I always carried, into his heart. He looked at me with a mix of shock, confusion, and pain, as if he had finally remembered something. With his last bit of strength, he managed to say two words, &amp;ldquo;The pocket.&amp;rdquo; I rolled my eyes at him. My dress didn&amp;rsquo;t have any pockets. Suddenly, the scene before me shifted, and I was engulfed in memories. I recalled the prison where I was once held captive, instinctively reaching into my pocket and finding the Ender Pearl that had once saved me. I also remembered the tightly wrapped officer. It was you all along, but why?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>An intense headache struck me, and I fainted. When I woke up again, I found myself in the Duke&amp;rsquo;s castle prison. &amp;ldquo;Your Highness, the assassin-dancer is here. The Duke is dead.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Good.&amp;rdquo; I heard a voice speaking, a voice filled with fear. It was so familiar, how could he still be alive? Why did the guards address him as &amp;ldquo;Your Highness&amp;rdquo;? Years of court performance had honed my strong psychological resilience, allowing me to easily compose myself and await the mysterious twist of fate.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The face, familiar yet unfamiliar, suddenly appeared and shattered all my elegance. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t give up, but I was also happy. The complex emotions almost engulfed me completely: &amp;ldquo;Why? Why are you still alive?&amp;rdquo; His cold and stern expression remained unchanged: &amp;ldquo;You killed my brother. We are twins.&amp;rdquo; He entered the prison cell, gripping my jaw with a cold and indifferent expression that seemed to hold a hint of a smile: &amp;ldquo;You did well, so what do you want for your next mode of death? Burning at the stake or the iron maiden?&amp;rdquo; I looked at his face, sharp and emotionless, and I understood. Suddenly, I laughed wildly and madly: &amp;ldquo;Ah, ten years ago, beneath the Witch Ridge, it was you! It wasn&amp;rsquo;t him after all!&amp;rdquo; He still showed no expression, his eyebrows slightly furrowing before he let go, as if he understood why I suddenly shouted about the events of ten years ago.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He ordered the guards to step back, and as someone restrained with iron shackles, I posed no threat to him. He sat in a chair and asked me, &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t you want to know why?&amp;rdquo; I replied, &amp;ldquo;Who are you exactly?&amp;rdquo; He calmly said, &amp;ldquo;You are indeed naive enough. You cooperated with me to accomplish perfect slaughter. I owe my position to you.&amp;rdquo; He continued, &amp;ldquo;You killed the prince. We both took an interest in you. Apparently, he was just as naive as you, falling deeper and suffering more. The reputation of the witch after the priestess is well-deserved.&amp;rdquo; I asked, &amp;ldquo;During these years, who was it that was with me? Was it you or him?&amp;rdquo; He chuckled softly, &amp;ldquo;Sometimes it was me, sometimes it was him. So, you still couldn&amp;rsquo;t distinguish? That fool pretended to be my officer ten years ago, distributing ender pearls everywhere. I even laughed at his kindness. It didn&amp;rsquo;t matter if a few slaves escaped; it was laughable that they died at the hands of slaves. Furthermore, I have a question. The poison was enough to kill him, even to let you escape unharmed. Why the need for this extra step? Perhaps he couldn&amp;rsquo;t smell that scent, but I could. I knew it was poison.&amp;rdquo; I stared at his deep blue yet cold eyes for a moment, then turned my head, refusing to answer. He continued, &amp;ldquo;Your crude extraction methods left so many traces even in your own home. I had a friend investigate, and it became clear that you had sinister intentions. So, I used you while you were using me, but I truly didn&amp;rsquo;t expect you to be the runaway slave.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Before leaving, he instructed the guards to take me to the public execution ground after lunch, where I would be burned at the stake. In the prison, I laughed manically. Did you really think that killing me would solve everything and stabilize the country? Yes, I once believed I was the hunter, but now I realize I am the hunted. On the public execution platform, I continued to laugh carelessly. He approached the stake and asked me, &amp;ldquo;Is this how it ends? Weren&amp;rsquo;t you supposed to be clever?&amp;rdquo; I looked towards the crowd gathering in the distance, a smile on my lips. &amp;ldquo;Is it over? No, it&amp;rsquo;s just the beginning.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Explain yourself, or&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; His voice carried a hint of impatience. I turned my head to look at him, my eyes filled with three parts pity and seven parts amusement. &amp;ldquo;Or what? What else can you do besides killing me? Do you think that by killing me, you can escape judgment? You accused me of being a witch, so I curse this city, I curse you.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;What else have you done?&amp;rdquo; His brow furrowed deeply, on the verge of exploding. But I remained silent, smiling once again as I looked into the distance, as if searching for something in the deep blue sky. As his patience wore thin, I slowly closed my eyes, allowing the flames to consume me, savoring the requiem of death that I had designed for myself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>THE END&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>IELTS Writing Course Note 07 FlowChart and Map Essay</title><link>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-07-flowchart-and-map-essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-07-flowchart-and-map-essay/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.statically.io/gh/Misakaou/imagestorage@master/20230702/IELTS-Writing-Course-Note-07-FlowChart-and-Map-Essay.27ybe1oxgbk0.webp" alt="Featured image of post IELTS Writing Course Note 07 FlowChart and Map Essay" />&lt;p>Source of this article: &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-07-flowchart-and-map-essay/" >MoeomuBlog&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="flow-chart">Flow Chart&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="first-words">First words&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>First&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>At the first stage / step&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Initially&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>In the beginning&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Beginning at X stage&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Next&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Then&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Subsequently&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>In the next / subsequent step&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>in the following phase&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Finally&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>In the concluding phase&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="combine-steps">Combine steps&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>and then / which then&lt;/li>
&lt;li>follow&lt;/li>
&lt;li>after&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="additional-information">Additional information&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>square&lt;/li>
&lt;li>rectangle&lt;/li>
&lt;li>sphere&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="flowchart-overview-paragraph">FlowChart: Overview paragraph&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="steps">Steps&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>X consists of / involves three stages&lt;/li>
&lt;li>X is comprised / composed of three phases&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Three main stages are shown on the diagram that illustrates X&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="evaluation">Evaluation&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Evaluation: simple / complex&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Core material or tool&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Compare multi stage&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Final destination&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="map">Map&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="directions--there-be">Directions + There be&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>To the north, there is an undeveloped beach.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="inversion-directions--verb--subject">Inversion (Directions + Verb + Subject)&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>On the north is situated a fountain.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="active-and-passive-sentences">Active and passive sentences&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>lie
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Building A lies on the north side.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>be situated / located / sited
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Building B is sited on the north side.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="start-with-a-change">Start with a Change&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>One change&amp;hellip; Another change&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>can be seen / is made to&lt;/li>
&lt;li>One change is made to the location of the entrance.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="azimuth-expression">Azimuth expression&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>in / to / on&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>One side of a large area
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>to / in / on&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A direction in a limited area
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Inside: in the east of B&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Outside: to the ease of B&lt;/li>
&lt;li>On the edge: on the east side of B&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Part
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>in the northern part&lt;/li>
&lt;li>on the northern side&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Road
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>an east-west road&lt;/li>
&lt;li>a road running east to west&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Corner
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>at the corner / turn&lt;/li>
&lt;li>at the junction&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Occupy
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>occupy the area&lt;/li>
&lt;li>area being covered by&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="map-overview-paragraph">Map: Overview paragraph&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>2 sentences.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Overall evaluation&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>IELTS Writing Course Note 06 Diagram Essay</title><link>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-06-diagram-essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-06-diagram-essay/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.statically.io/gh/Misakaou/imagestorage@master/20230702/IELTS-Writing-Course-Note-06-Diagram-Essay.6t45w80e8veo.webp" alt="Featured image of post IELTS Writing Course Note 06 Diagram Essay" />&lt;p>Source of this article: &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-06-diagram-essay/" >MoeomuBlog&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="change-the-subject">Change the subject&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="start-with-a-number">Start with a Number&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>1% of the Yemen&amp;rsquo;s population was in / among / belonged to the 0-14 year old group in the year 2000.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="use-there-be">Use &amp;ldquo;There be&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>There was a proportion of 1% Yemen&amp;rsquo;s population belonging / that belonged to the 0-14 year old age group in the year 2000.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="start-with-an-info-dimension">Start with an info dimension&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The year 2000 saw a percentage of 1% of Yemen&amp;rsquo;s population among / belonging to the 0-14 year old group.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The 0-14 year olds made up a proportion of 1% of Yemen&amp;rsquo;s population in 2000.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Yemen&amp;rsquo;s population was composed of 1% individuals aged 0-14 years old in 2000.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="start-with-an-evaluation">Start with an evaluation&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The highest proportion of Yemen&amp;rsquo;s population in 2000 was among the 0-14 year old group.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="subject--object">Subject / Object&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The consumption of petrol and oil has been the highest, and it is projected to remain the first place until 2030.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>People preferred to use petrol and oil s their main sources of energy.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="tense">Tense&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="past-simple">Past simple&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>will do&lt;/li>
&lt;li>is expected to do&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>is projected to do&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="continuous">Continuous&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>was increasing&amp;hellip; until&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="perfect">Perfect&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="merge-data">Merge data&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="evaluation--specific-values-or-trends">Evaluation + specific values or trends&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A is the highest over time, at 50 in the year M and 100 in the year N.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A experienced a steady growth, rising from 50 to 100.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="before--after">Before + After&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>and then / which then
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>In the year M, figure A is 10, and then / which then increased to 20 in the year N.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>follow
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A reached a peak of 50% in the year M, followed by a O-year decline to 40%.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A reached a peak of 50% in the year M, with a following decline for O years to 40%.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>after
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>After an increase from 10% to 15%, figure A dropped to nearly zero in the year N.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="evaluation--specific-values-or-trends--before--after">Evaluation + specific values or trends + Before + After&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The year N saw a rise to 30 for figure A, around 2 times / twofold / doubling higher than this figure (15) in the year M.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="main-clause--contrast--analogy">Main clause + contrast / analogy&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Conjunctions
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>while / although&lt;/li>
&lt;li>While figure A recorded a significant growth from 30 to 40 by the year M, this figure remained basically unchanged between 35 and 40 from year O to N.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Adverb
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>however / similarly / in contrast&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A saw a noticeable decline. Similarly, figure B decreased sharply.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A saw a noticeable decline. In contrast, figure B remained constantly over time.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Adjective
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>trend / patter&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A saw a noticeable increase. A different pattern was seen in figure B, which decreased sharply.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Before the year O, figure A decreased noticeable while figure B recorded an upward trend. In contrast, similar patterns were seen between year O and N, during which both figure A and B decreased gradually.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="other">Other&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="year">year&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>18 year old group&lt;/li>
&lt;li>people aged 18 years old&lt;/li>
&lt;li>18 year olds = 18 year old people&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>IELTS Writing Course Note 05 Diagram Essay</title><link>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-05-diagram-essay/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-05-diagram-essay/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.statically.io/gh/Misakaou/imagestorage@master/20230701/IELTS-Writing-Course-Note-05-Diagram-Essay.7gcpp95llhts.webp" alt="Featured image of post IELTS Writing Course Note 05 Diagram Essay" />&lt;p>Source of this article: &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-05-diagram-essay/" >MoeomuBlog&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="overall-rules">Overall Rules&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Well organized&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Different expressions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Multi data merged&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="rewrite-paragraph">Rewrite paragraph&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Copy diagram title&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="overview-paragraph">Overview paragraph&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Rough shape&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>e.g.: In general / In sum / Overall, a higher proportion of males choose to study STEM fields, while more females prefer to study humanity-related subjects. Moreover, it is noticeable that there is a significant disparity / difference in major choices between genders across various fields of study.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Extreme values
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>and also add it in detail paragraph.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="detail-paragraph">Detail paragraph&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="split-group">Split group&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Select the paragraph with the highest number of items as the basis for grouping&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Select the grouping latitude that contains all chart dimensions&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="writing-order">Writing order&lt;/h3>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Extreme values (2-3 clauses) and related content&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Values with similarity (2-3 clauses)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Supply self-selected values&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h3 id="change-data-object-words">Change data object words&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Noun + A + B + C + D.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A + Noun + B + C + D.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-value--percentage--trend">Expressions: value &amp;amp; percentage &amp;amp; trend&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Value
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>figure / data / number / amount / value&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Percentage
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>percentage / proportion / rate / ratio / share&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Trend
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>trend / pattern&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="relationship-between-value-and-sentence">Relationship between value and sentence&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>at / with&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A similar trend can be seen in figure A with an increase from 5 to 10.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A remained unchanged, at 10 from year M to N.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A is 10 in year M, with an increase to 20 in year N.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-proportion">Expressions: Proportion&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>5% of B is A.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A represents 5% of B.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A represents a proportion of 5% of B.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>accounts&lt;/li>
&lt;li>makes up&lt;/li>
&lt;li>comprises&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>5% of B is composed / made up of A.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>5% of B is from / belongs to A.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-other">Expressions: Other&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A is the highest, at 5% in the year M.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>There was a increase in / for figure A.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The value increased by 5%。&lt;/li>
&lt;li>see / experience / record / show
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A saw an increase&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The year M / Group Experienced / recorded an increase&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Approximate number
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>about&lt;/li>
&lt;li>around&lt;/li>
&lt;li>approximately&lt;/li>
&lt;li>just / slightly - over / below&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A showed an upward / downward trend, rising from 5 to 10.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Stable value
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>verb: remain constantly at a level / 10&lt;/li>
&lt;li>noun: experienced a period of stability&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Especial value
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>except / besides / despite / in spite of&lt;/li>
&lt;li>e.g.: Figure A recorded a general increase from year M to N, despite a slight fluctuation between year X to Y.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-increase-and-decline">Expressions: Increase and decline&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>rise / increase / grow / growth / climb (from a decline)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>decline / fall / drop&lt;/li>
&lt;li>e.g.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A rose from 5 to 10.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO, rising from 5 to 10.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A experienced a fall from 5 to 10.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO, with a fall from 5 to 10.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-fluctuation">Expressions: Fluctuation&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>vary / variation&lt;/li>
&lt;li>fluctuate / fluctuation&lt;/li>
&lt;li>e.g.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The figure vary / fluctuate between 10 and 15.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The figure recorded d a variation / fluctuation between 10 and 15.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-multiplier">Expressions: Multiplier&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>verb.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>double / triple / quadruple&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A double / triple / quadruple the original value.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>X times
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A is 3 times the amount of Figure B.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A rose 3 times the amount of Figure B.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>two / three / fourfold
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>There was a threefold increase in / for figure A.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Modifiers
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>almost / more / less than&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>More than / less than
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>be greater than / over / exceed + value&lt;/li>
&lt;li>be less than / below + value&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Overtake
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>overtake / take over / surpass / take the lead over&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A over took figure B in the year O.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>With in range
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>within / less than / no more than + value&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The difference between figure A and B is no more than 5 from year M to N.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-max-value">Expressions: Max value&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>peak&lt;/li>
&lt;li>highest point&lt;/li>
&lt;li>lowest point&lt;/li>
&lt;li>reach a lowest point / highest point / peak&lt;/li>
&lt;li>verb synonym: achieve / hit / attain&lt;/li>
&lt;li>reach a lowest point / highest point / peak of 90%&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-same-value">Expressions: Same value&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A and B are almost equal / same in value.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A is approximately the same as B.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>There is little difference between figure A and B.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-rebound">Expressions: Rebound&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A rebound from&amp;hellip; to&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Figure A recorded a rebound from&amp;hellip; to&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-gap">Expressions: Gap&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>gap / difference / disparity&lt;/li>
&lt;li>widen / increase / grow / become larger&lt;/li>
&lt;li>narrow / decrease / reduce / become smaller&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The gap / difference between figure A and B widened from year M.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="expressions-time">Expressions: Time&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>By the year M, figure A&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Starting from the year M, figure A&lt;/li>
&lt;li>From the year M to N during, figure A&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The year M marked a point when figure A reached a peak.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>when + time point
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A increased to 10 in the year O, when figure B decreased to the same value 20.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>which + value
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>In year O, figure A over took figure B, which then decline gradually to 10.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>preposition + witch + time period
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Figure A increased from 10 to 20 from the year M to N, during which figure B remained constantly at 15.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>IELTS Writing Course Note 04 Compare(Outweigh) and Report Essay</title><link>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-04-compareoutweigh-and-report-essay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-04-compareoutweigh-and-report-essay/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.statically.io/gh/Misakaou/imagestorage@master/20230630/IELTS-Writing-Course-Note-04-Compare(Outweigh)-and-Report-Essay.3sgs2f8b61kw.webp" alt="Featured image of post IELTS Writing Course Note 04 Compare(Outweigh) and Report Essay" />&lt;p>Source of this article: &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-04-compareoutweigh-and-report-essay/" >MoeomuBlog&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="outweigh">Outweigh&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="attention">Attention&lt;/h3>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Must be neutral.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Must lean toward a certain point of view.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h3 id="write-outweigh-essay-sub-paragraph-first-sentence">Write Outweigh essay sub paragraph first sentence&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="131">1+3+1&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Same as Lesson1.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="121">1+2+1&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>First, one advantage of X is that&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>However, we also need to note / acknowledge the (ADDITION) negative aspects of X.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>more concerning / alarming&lt;/li>
&lt;li>less concerning / relatively minor&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In fact, X can cause more concerning harm to&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="write-overview-paragraph">Write overview paragraph&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="paraphrase-topic">paraphrase topic&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Same as previous.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="give-opinion">give opinion&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>I believe that the drawbacks of this trend outweigh the benefits.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="write-ending-paragraph">Write ending paragraph&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>conclusion&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Although X may offer benefits to A and B, the adverse effects on C and D are more substantial and should be taken into consideration.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="complete-outweigh-example">Complete Outweigh Example&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>An increasing number of people are spending a significant amount of time on social media, interacting with friends through communication and gaming.
First, the widespread availability of the internet and social media has greatly improved our ability to communicate.
Furthermore, another advantage of social media is associated with its engaging and immersive experience.
However, we need also note one relatively minor drawback of the social media.
To conclude, while social media can be addictive, it is more important for us to acknowledge its positive aspects in terms of the enhancement of people&amp;rsquo;s communication and experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="logic-chain-writing-contrast">Logic chain writing: Contrast&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="rather-than--instead-of">rather than / instead of&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>SVO, -S / -V / -O.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Every individual possesses the capability to grow into responsible and contributing members of their community, rather than / instead of participating in actions that cause harm of destruction to society.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>would rather than do than do&lt;/li>
&lt;li>rather do than doing&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="without--n--on-the-contrary--otherwise">without + N / on the contrary / otherwise&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>SVO. On the contrary / Otherwise / Without adv., SVO.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="without-which">without which&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>, without which = without + adv.,&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="in-fact">in fact&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>connecting the truth&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>However, it is also true that mental attitude is a vital component of success in sports. In fact, some people argue that mental attitude is even more important than physical fitness.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="logic-chain-writing-concurrent">Logic chain writing: Concurrent&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="and--or">and / or&lt;/h3>
&lt;h3 id="as-well-as">as well as&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>as well as do&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>as well as doing&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="not-only-but-also--while">not only but also / while&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Both before and after are complete sentences.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="report">Report&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="write-report-essay-sub-paragraph-first-sentence">Write Report essay sub paragraph first sentence&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="report-121">Report: 1+2+1&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The main reason / consequence for X is&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To address / combat this issue, A and B should take on / assume the responsibility / take appropriate measures.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="report-131">Report: 1+3+1&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>One reason / consequence for X is&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To address this issue, A and B should take on the responsibility / take appropriate measures.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Moreover, A and B should also do&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="write-report-essay-sub-paragraph-second-sentence">Write Report essay sub paragraph second sentence&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>There are several reasons for this trend.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In this essay, I will explore / discuss the causes of X, and what can be done to reduce its effects.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="ending">Ending&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Same as previous.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="complete-report-example">Complete Report Example&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>The natural resources are being exploited and consumed by humans without stops. In this essay, I will explore the causes of consequences of X, and what can be done to reduce its effects.&lt;br>
The main impacts of the overconsumption of natural resources is the degradation of the overall ecosystems.&lt;br>
To combat this issue, it is crucial for government to take on its responsibility.&lt;br>
In conclusion, given the disastrous consequences of depleting natural resources, it is crucial for governments to play a key role in ensuring their sustainable use and protection for future generations.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="mixture">Mixture&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="characteristics">Characteristics&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Why does this happen?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Do you think it is a positive or negative development&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="write-mixture-essay-sub-paragraph-first-sentence">Write Mixture essay sub paragraph first sentence&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="mixture-131">Mixture: 1+3+1&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>One reason for X is&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Moreover, another reason for X is..&lt;/li>
&lt;li>However, I think X can also bring negative effects to..&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="write-mixture-overview-paragraph">Write Mixture overview paragraph&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>I believe X is beneficial / harmful for&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="complete-mixture-example">Complete Mixture Example&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Some parents tend to exert excessive pressure on their children. I believe it is generally a positive trend.&lt;br>
One reason for this trend concerns the education.&lt;br>
Moreover, another reason for such a trend is that it can help children regulate their own behaviour.&lt;br>
However, as for me, too much pressure can leave children with little time to enjoy their hobbies.&lt;br>
In conclusion, many parents choose to put pressure on their children in order to help them become knowledgeable and responsible individuals who can better adapt to society. While this can have its benefits, I believe too much pressure can also prevent children from pursuing their true interests.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>IELTS Writing Course Note 03 Discuss Essay</title><link>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-03-discuss-essay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-03-discuss-essay/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.statically.io/gh/Misakaou/imagestorage@master/20230630/IELTS-Writing-Course-Note-03-Discuss-Essay.573jmp76c1kw.webp" alt="Featured image of post IELTS Writing Course Note 03 Discuss Essay" />&lt;p>Source of this article: &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-03-discuss-essay/" >MoeomuBlog&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="segmentation-method">Segmentation method&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Stating the first preconceived idea.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Stating the second preconceived idea.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Give our own opinion.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="write-sub-argument-paragraph-first-sentence">Write sub-argument paragraph first sentence&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>First, some people argue that + first preconceived idea.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>To begin with, they believe that&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>For another, they also claim that&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>However, other people argue that + second preconceived idea.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>On the one hand, it could be argued by other people that&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>On the other hand, a different perspective / proponent / opponent is held by others who believe that&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="use-persona">Use persona&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="people">People&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>first person: we&lt;/li>
&lt;li>third person: people / individuals / everyone&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="specific-people">Specific people&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>avoid singular person&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="logic-chain-writing-enumeration">Logic chain writing: Enumeration&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="grammar-rules">Grammar rules&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>2 items tied: A and B&lt;/li>
&lt;li>3 items tied: A, B, and C&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Attention
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Instead of using &lt;em>etc.&lt;/em>, use &lt;em>and other X (related) Sth.&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>e.g.: &lt;em>obesity, heart diseases, and other health related issues.&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="connect">Connect&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>such as
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>I don&amp;rsquo;t like people such as him.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I like my pets, such as the white dog and black cat.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>include
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>SVO, including A, B, and C&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO. This may / can include A, B, and C&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A and B are two ways
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Encouraging innovation and investing in education are two possible ways.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>SVO: SVO.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO: noun.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO: A, B, and C.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A, B, and C &amp;ndash; C.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>,
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>SVO, SVingO. / Error e.g.: SVO, SVO. (run-on)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>imaging (imperative sentence)
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Imaging + Noun.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>e.g.: Imaging a student, who..&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Imaging that + sentence.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>e.g.: Imaging that a literature student&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>while&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="logic-chain-writing-concession">Logic chain writing: Concession&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>although / while
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Although SVO, SVO.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>in spite of / despite / notwithstanding
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>despite noun, SVO.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>despite the fact that + Homophobic clauses, SVO.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>nonetheless / nevertheless&lt;/li>
&lt;li>admittedly
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Admittedly / we need to admit that&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>It is true that&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>There is no denying that&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="write-first-and-ending-paragraph">Write First and Ending paragraph&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="first-sentence">First sentence&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>There are two different perspectives regarding X.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>There has been a conflict about X.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="give-opinion">Give opinion&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>I am more inclined to agree with A.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I have a stronger inclination towards concurring with A.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I believe there is a way to resolve this conflict.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I believe a resolution to this conflict can be achieved.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In my opinion, X can also bring benefits / harmful impacts to&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In my opinion, there are other positive / negative impacts of X to consider.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In my opinion, while X may have negative effects, they can be overcome with solutions.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I hold the view that both opinions all have their merits. Form my perspective, there are benefits to be found in both opinions.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>e.g.: In conclusion, while advertising have some drawbacks, since it can bring positive effects to the economy, including promoting both innovation and employment, I believe it is generally beneficial to the society as a whole.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>e.g.: In my opinion, while advertisement may have fore mentioned negative effects, solutions are available to overcome these issues. In conclusion, despite the harmful effects of some types of advertisement, I believe that the government can take appropriate measures to address these issues and ensure that advertising is conducted in a responsible and beneficial manner for the public.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>IELTS Writing Course Note 02 Opinion Essay</title><link>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-02-opinion-essay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-02-opinion-essay/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.statically.io/gh/Misakaou/imagestorage@master/20230630/IELTS-Writing-Course-Note-02-Opinion-Essay.3io6hcc5uji8.webp" alt="Featured image of post IELTS Writing Course Note 02 Opinion Essay" />&lt;p>Source of this article: &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-02-opinion-essay/" >MoeomuBlog&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="write-first-sentence-of-paragraph">Write first sentence of paragraph&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="121-lopsided">1+2+1 Lopsided&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>First, one argument for / in favour of X is&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Second, another argument for / in favour of X is&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="121-neutral">1+2+1 Neutral&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>First, one argument for / in favour of X is&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>However, one argument against X is&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="replace">Replace&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="argument">Argument&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>reason&lt;/li>
&lt;li>point&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="whole-sentence">Whole sentence&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>there be
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>However, there are also arguments against X.&lt;br>
However, there are also counterargument to X.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>X can also bring benefit / harmful impact to&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>usage: &lt;strong>MUST NOT&lt;/strong> in first paragraph&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="needed-pronoun">Needed Pronoun&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>this
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>use alone: refers to whole sentence&lt;/li>
&lt;li>this + special content: refers to special detail&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>that
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>do not use&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>these
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>refers to plural noun&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>those
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>those + who&amp;hellip;: &lt;code>This can lead to a widening of the gap between those who have the access to the internet and those who do not.&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>such
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>similar to this but cannot refers to whole sentence, such = this + those&lt;/li>
&lt;li>usage
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>such + plural noun: such approaches&lt;/li>
&lt;li>such + a / an + singular noun: such an approach&lt;/li>
&lt;li>such + adj. + noun: such helpful approaches&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>so&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="logic-chain-writing-conditional-relationships">Logic chain writing: Conditional relationships&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="if">if&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Recycling of waste is made mandatory by law. This can drive people to comply.&lt;br>
If recycling of waste is made mandatory by law, people will comply.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>replace IF
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>provided that&lt;/li>
&lt;li>on condition that&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>extend the logic chain
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>If SVO, SVO, leading to&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If A occurs, but not -A, then B occurs. Conversely, B does not occur.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>e.g.: If the recycling of waste is made mandatory by law, people are more likely to comply.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>e.g.: If the recycling of waste is made mandatory by law, rather than through willingness, people are more likely to comply. Otherwise, the waste will be disposed in a careless manner.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Only if / As long as&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="no-matter-what">No matter what&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>replace
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>when&lt;/li>
&lt;li>where&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>examples
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>People can easily find information they need on the internet, no matter what their field of study is.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>People can easily find information they need on the internet no matter / regardless of their field of study.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="whether">Whether&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>examples
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>People can easily find information they need on the internet, whether their field of study is art or science.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>People can easily find information they need on the internet regardless of their field of study, whether they are major in science, art, or any other subjects.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>whether be
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&amp;hellip; whether it (should) be in science&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>be it in science, art, or&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="extend-logic-chain">Extend logic chain&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>A can do X.&lt;/code> -&amp;gt; &lt;code>A can do X. In particular / especially, A1, can do better.&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>A can do X.&lt;/code> -&amp;gt; &lt;code>A can do X. In particular, A1, who / which has certain characteristic, more likely to do X.&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>A can do X.&lt;/code> -&amp;gt; &lt;code>This is especially true / beneficial / harmful for A1. + who + certain characteristic&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="write-overview">Write overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="part">Part&lt;/h3>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>synonymic rewriting the topic&lt;/li>
&lt;li>write general view&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h3 id="argumentative-topics">Argumentative topics&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Attitudes are given for each of the two branches of opinion.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>First, write disagree branch, then, write agree branch.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Attention: There is no need to repeat the topic, because they are merge with each other.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Example
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;code>While learning about local history is beneficial for students, I believe that being knowledgable of world history is also necessary in the modern age.&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="write-ending">Write ending&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>same as Lesson1&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>IELTS Writing Course Note 01 Disadvantage and Advantage Essay</title><link>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-01-disadvantage-and-advantage-essay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-01-disadvantage-and-advantage-essay/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.statically.io/gh/Misakaou/imagestorage@master/20230630/IELTS-Writing-Course-Note-01-Disadvantage-and-Advantage-Essay.1t76xiwq5tx.webp" alt="Featured image of post IELTS Writing Course Note 01 Disadvantage and Advantage Essay" />&lt;p>Source of this article: &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.moeomu.com/posts/ielts-writing-course-note-01-disadvantage-and-advantage-essay/" >MoeomuBlog&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="write-the-first-word">Write the first word&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Yes, we can write &amp;ldquo;First, Second, Third&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;, it is simple but &lt;strong>not affective&lt;/strong> the score.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>For a &lt;strong>paragraph&lt;/strong>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>First / Firstly / First of all&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Second / Secondly / Moreover / Furthermore&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Third / Thirdly / Lastly / At last&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>For a &lt;strong>subargument&lt;/strong>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>To begin with / One concern / Specifically / Primarily&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Additionally / In addition / Moreover / Furthermore / What&amp;rsquo;s more / Another concern / Also / For another&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="write-first-sentence-of-paragraph">Write first sentence of paragraph&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Respond to &lt;em>agree or disagree&lt;/em> / &lt;em>positive or negative&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="for-121-lopsided-views">For &lt;em>1+2+1 lopsided views&lt;/em>&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>First, one positive aspect of X is...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>Moreover, another positive aspect of X is... / Moreover, X can also bring another benefit to...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="for-122-neutral-views">For &lt;em>1+2+2 neutral views&lt;/em>&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>First, one positive aspect of X is...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>However, one negative aspect of X is...&lt;/code> or &lt;code>However, it is important to note / acknowledge the negative aspect of X.&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="for-131-neutral-views">For &lt;em>1+3+1 neutral views&lt;/em>&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>First, one positive aspect of X is...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>Moreover, X can also bring a benefit to...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>However, it is important to acknowledge the negative aspect of X.&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="for-131-lopsided-viewscause-problem">For &lt;em>1+3+1 lopsided views&lt;/em>(cause problem)&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>First, one positive aspect of X is...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>Moreover, another positive aspect of X is...&lt;/code> or &lt;code>Moreover, X can bring a further benefit to...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>Lastly, yet another positive aspect of X is...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="more-examples">More examples&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>benefit usages:&lt;/strong> X can bring benefits to / X has the benefit for / X is beneficial for / X can benefit&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>disadvantages usages:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>X has disadvantages / drawbacks / shortcomings related to&lt;/li>
&lt;li>X can have negative / adverse effects / impacts on&lt;/li>
&lt;li>X can negatively impact&lt;/li>
&lt;li>X can be harmful / detrimental / damaging to&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="write-our-own-views">Write our own views&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Do not give direct result
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>First, one positive aspect of promoting public transportation is the improved convenience and effectiveness of the residents&amp;rsquo; living.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Using the Argumentative Corpus and Advanced Vocabulary. Download file: &lt;a class="link" href="IELTS-Essay-Corpus.zip" >IELTS-Essay-Corpus.zip&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Using &lt;a class="link" href="https://disk.moeomu.com/Global-OneDrive/VideoTutorial/Language-%5B%E4%B9%9D%E5%88%86%E5%AD%A6%E9%95%BF%5D%5B6%E6%9C%88%5D%E9%9B%85%E6%80%9D%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C21%E5%A4%A9%E5%86%B27%E8%AE%A1%E5%88%92/Documents.zip" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>necessary documents (Chinese)&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Watching &lt;a class="link" href="https://disk.moeomu.com/Global-OneDrive/VideoTutorial/Language-%5B%E4%B9%9D%E5%88%86%E5%AD%A6%E9%95%BF%5D%5B6%E6%9C%88%5D%E9%9B%85%E6%80%9D%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C21%E5%A4%A9%E5%86%B27%E8%AE%A1%E5%88%92" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Videos (Chinese)&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>More generalized sentences
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>First, one positive aspect of promoting public transportation is related to / associated with / concerns people&amp;rsquo;s daily lives. By doing this, the convenience and effectiveness of the residents&amp;rsquo; mobility can be greatly enhanced.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="logic-chain-writing-causality">Logic chain writing: Causality&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="because">because&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>in&lt;code>A, because B&lt;/code>, A is more important&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="since">since&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>in &lt;code>A, since B&lt;/code>, B is more important&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="lead-in-a-lead-to-b">lead: in &lt;code>A lead to B&lt;/code>&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>SVO. This can lead to A, leading to B.&lt;/code>, same importance
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>Government increased the capacity of the road network. This can lead to more room for cars to travel, leading to an increased efficiency of traffic flow as a result.&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>Because SVO, SVO, leading to...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>By doing sth., SVO, leading to...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>SVO, leading to / which can lead to + Result&lt;/code>, SVO is more important&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Synonyms
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>SVO, resulting in sth.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO, allowing / enabling sb. to do sth.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO, contributing to&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO, encouraging / driving / motivating sb. to do sth.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO, which plays an important role in doing sth.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO, promoting / reducing&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO, strengthening / weakening&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SVO, making it easier / more difficult to do&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>factor, &lt;code>A lead to B.&lt;/code> = &lt;code>A is a contributing factor to B.&lt;/code> = &lt;code>A is a factor that contributes to B.&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="therefore--as-a-result--consequently">therefore / as a result / consequently&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Usage: Lead a complete sentence, &lt;code>SVO. Therefore, SVO.&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Conclusion: Highly summative.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="thus--in-turn--thereby">thus / in turn / thereby&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Usage: Append to sentences that already have a cause-and-effect relationship to further enhance the tone. &lt;code>SVO. This, in turn, can lead to...&lt;/code> or &lt;code>SVO, thus leading to...&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>which means
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Usage: Lead a cause-and-effect relationship. &lt;code>SVO, which means (that) + Result(complete sentence)&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>By increasing the capacity of the road network, there are more room for cars to travel, which means this approach can increase the efficiency of traffic flow as a result.&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="write-overview">Write overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="100--70--50">100% / 70% / 50%&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>I believe that this is a completely positive / negative trend.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I believe that this is generally a positive / negative trend.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I believe that this trend has
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>both positive and negative sides.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>advantages and disadvantages.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>benefits and drawbacks.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="specific">Specific&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="personal">Personal&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>on a personal level&lt;/li>
&lt;li>on a societal level&lt;/li>
&lt;li>on an environmental level&lt;/li>
&lt;li>on an educational level&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="life">Life&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>on the level of daily life&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="write-ending-paragraph">Write ending paragraph&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>In conclusion, X can bring benefits in terms of A and B. However, it is also crucial to acknowledge the potential negative impacts. This can include C and D.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item></channel></rss>